Hm.
To this universe, I'm Kuni-chan.
This is my T-shirt.
Thank you very much.
Milori Ohana.
Cute!
Big size is cute.
Cute
My solo concert t-shirt
I think this is actually called "Sana Morohashi Solo Concert".
Kanji? It was in Kanji Japanese.
But Mr. Tochihara said it would be better in English. Mr. Tochihara said it would be better in English, so it's now in English.
It turned out cool!
This outfit I'm wearing today also has flowers!
Ta-da!
For the first time, there's a word for Budokan.
I like it so much I've worn it many times!
I even decided on the back.
I decided everything myself.
Of course, I consulted with Sashihara-san, but...
I decided on the back of the kimono all by myself.
The reason why I voted for the handwritten note was that I couldn't say the line "Micah" for the rest of my life, which I didn't have in the first place.
I was wondering when the fans would be able to say it, so I said, "I'll say it.
I think they decided to punish me if I didn't know the line before the show.
So I wasn't supposed to vote for the handwritten notes, but I'm going to vote for the handwritten notes.
The first song is a little bit my voice, and everyone thinks "Oh, the first song is definitely my voice," but the second song is the best, eh, the second song is the best.
But the second song is the most, what is it? What are they going to sing? What is it going to be? That's where we come in.
Shuqipi. Everyone was very nervous, so I asked, "Are you okay? Why did you put Shukipi in there? Soratsu, you're never going to be able to say your lines, are you? I'm sure you can't say a word..." That's how it started.
The lyrics of "Genki Idol" are a little different. It started, and during Genki Idol, the lyrics are a little different.
Not the pink frilly ones.
It's not pink and frilly, it's green and frilly.
It's not pink, but green.
And to those who mixed red and white
Thank you to those who mix blue and yellow.
Actually...
Nervous?
I seriously don't know. I can't wait to sing! I can't wait to sing!
I'm going to have fun, even if it's only for a short time.
I'll do my best.
Good morning. This is Morohasana.
Today is my solo concert, and I will do my best, so please join me.
It's my first time, so I won't change anymore.
Will you make something good together?
I will do my best by all means. I look forward to working with you.
Rehearsal, please.
Yes, I will.
It's fun, but tough.
How do artists do it?
Shkipia?
Shkipia lyrics do it.
Shkipia, shkipia, shkipia, shkipia
Always up day White is Kewakimi
Justic. Me.
Here I am.
I feel like I'm gonna lose 5kg today
That's how high-calorie it is. So high in calories.
Hey, guys.
We're having fun.
Yeah?
It's fun! It's so much fun.
I'm having so much fun, even though I should be in a real hurry.
You have to have fun.
It's a waste of time if you're nervous.
Have fun!
Mr. Sasahara came up with the lyrics this time!
I'm very nervous, but this is the first time I'm going to perform it
I'm going to sing with all my heart.
Still, please listen to the song!
The treasure is green!
I'm so glad we didn't do just one performance!
I mean, it's like we've already done it once.
Yeah, it's really like one show, but it's like one show now.
You're singing the whole thing.
What? How much time do we have left, 3 hours?
Two hours? Oh, no.
Yes, sir.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Thank you very much.
Someone give me a yakiniku bento! I've got a lot of fat on my brain.
I think I'm in real trouble. I think I'm dying.
Oh, my brain is so strong, but I have to speak all in my back voice.
I didn't even know how to sing, so I tried to sing like I was supposed to, but I broke it.I didn't even know how to sing it, so I tried to sing it like it was supposed to be sung, but I broke it.
Here you go.
First of all, you were worried about your voice, right?
And then there's the lyrics.
Let's go over them together.
Yes. No, no, no.
Here's the next one.
Oh, I like it.
I like it.
Hello, what are you guys doing?
If it's Asaka's solo concert, I don't blame you.
Do you want to see a pattern?
Yeah.
It's special.
Oh...
Seriously, the lyrics.
I don't know what to do.
And the most unsettling
Memoir pin
Well, but most of all, I'll do my best to have fun, because it would be a waste if I'm nervous.
Because today is the only day.
So.
You can do it.
So, let's have fun today.
Yeah.
I thought of it myself, Setori.
That's right.That's right.
Let's have fun.
Everyone can have fun.
But I'm not nervous yet.
I can enjoy it a lot.
But you know, I've decided to celebrate my 5th anniversary. I did My Vice as a solo performer,
I wasn't nervous at all, and when I went up on the center stage, my hands got really stiff.
Actually, my hands got really stiff.
My body was not nervous.
My body wasn't nervous.
So I sang with both hands like this. I was cooing like this.
Well, everyone, it's time for your dream solo concert.
I know I asked you before, but do you have ours?
Do you have a towel?
Yes, I do.
Do you have your future penlight? Yes, I do.
Thank you. Okay, everyone, let's enjoy today until the end.
Well then, we will be leaving soon. Please wait for a while.
That's all for now.
Congratulations!
A big round of applause to all of you!
Three hearts.
You're gonna freak out.
Thank you for watching!
Oh man! It was fun!
It was really fun!
It was really good!
It was so much fun!
Who's to say it wasn't fun!
Who's to say it wasn't great!I don't know who to tell, but it's great!
Really?
It's so much fun!
Yeah!
You know what? It was fun!
That's all I can say.
But I can say that it's really fun.
I think it's fun.
It's because our fans are always there for us
It's because the fans have always supported us.
I'm really grateful for that.
Today, too, Midori's wearing all kinds of things
They wear, they carry my goods, and
And most of all
I thought of you the most.
What? What?
Since I was allowed to call out my voice
I'm so glad I did the solo concert.
I was really happy to do the solo concert.
And the MC was a lot of fun.
and I could hear everyone's
I was so happy to hear everyone's calls
I was so happy.
If the next show goes well
I hope we can do it again and again and again.
I hope we will be able to tour again.
I found a lot of things I need to work on
I will do my best!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!Thank you!
Yay!